// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is the closest planet to the sun?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
      "Neptune",
      "Mercury",
      "Earth",
      "Venus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many moons does Mars have? (earth has one moon)",
    answer: "two",
    options: [
      "two",
      "fewer than 50",
      "more than one",
      "fewer than 13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Where is the astroid belt? (between two planets)",
    answer: "between Mars and Jupiter",
    options: [
      "between Earth and Mars",
      "between Mars and Jupiter",
      "between Earth and Venus",
      "between Jupiter and Saturn"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What are the comets mostly made of?",
    answer: "snow, ice and dust",
    options: [
      "rusty metal",
      "hot, liquid rock",
      "snow, ice and dust",
      "poisonous liquid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The day on which the Sun's direct rays cross the celestial equator:",
    answer: "the equinox",
    options: [
      "the ecliptic",
      "the solstice",
      "the aphelion",
      "the equinox"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who invented the telescope? (father of observational astronomy)",
    answer: "Galileo",
    options: [
      "Johannes Kepler",
      "Galileo",
      "Hans Lippershey",
      "Hypatia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these objects is the farthest from the Sun?",
    answer: "90377 Sedna",
    options: [
      "Neptune",
      "Saturn",
      "90377 Sedna",
      "Kuiper belt"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies?",
    answer: "syzygy",
    options: [
      "sizzle",
      "symbology",
      "suzerinty",
      "syzygy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the smallest planet in the solar system by mass?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "Earth",
      "Mars",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the visible part of the Sun called?",
    answer: "the photosphere",
    options: [
      "the photosphere",
      "the lithosphere",
      "the atmosphere",
      "the stratosphere"
    ]
  },
];